Hi, my name is David Brown, and this is a reading writing class.
大家好，我叫戴维·布朗 (Dàiwéi Bùlǎng)，这是一堂读写课。
Hello, welcome. How are you?
你好，欢迎。你今天怎么样？
Hi, nice to meet you.
老师好，很高兴见到您。
Nice to meet you too. My name is David. What's your name?
我也很高兴见到你。我叫戴维。你叫什么名字？
My name is Francesco. Pleasure to meet you, David.
我叫弗朗切斯科 (Fúlǎngqiēsīkē)。很高兴认识您，戴维老师。
Nice to meet you, Francesco. Welcome.
很高兴认识你，弗朗切斯科同学。欢迎。
I see that you selected a lesson about Walt Whitman and his famous poem,
我看到您选择了一节关于沃尔特·惠特曼 (Wò'ěrtè Huìtèmàn) 和他著名诗歌的课程，
Oh, captain, my captain, a reading and writing class. Is that right?
《啊，船长！我的船长！》(Ā, chuánzhǎng! Wǒ de chuánzhǎng!)，一堂读写课。对吗？
Yes, that is correct.
是的，没错。
Okay, great.
好的，非常好。
So I'll tell you a little bit about Abraham Lincoln.
那么我来给你简单介绍一下亚伯拉罕·林肯 (Yàbólāhǎn Línkěn)。
You've probably heard of honest Abe before he was the 16th US president.
你可能听说过“诚实的艾布”(Chéngshí de Àibù) 这个绰号，他是美国第16任总统。
He was assassinated in 1865.
他于1865年遇刺身亡。
You might compare him to another famous leader. Do you know who this guy is?
你或许可以将他与另一位著名的领导人相比较。你知道这位是谁吗？
Yes, Francisco Morazán.
是的，弗朗西斯科·莫拉桑 (Fúlǎngxīsīkē Mòlāsāng)。
Francisco Morazán. Okay, so they're not the same, but they are very popular presidents, right?
弗朗西斯科·莫拉桑。好的，他们不尽相同，但都是非常受欢迎的总统，对吧？
Correct. Yes.
是的，没错。
So this question for us is what makes a good leader?
所以我们要讨论的问题是：怎样才算一个好的领导者？
Take a minute to think about it, and then you can share with me and talk about this.
花一分钟思考一下，然后你可以和我分享并讨论这个问题。
What makes a good leader in your opinion?
在你看来，怎样才算一个好的领导者？
Okay.
好的。
Do you want me to write it down or can I just start?
您是希望我写下来还是可以直接开始说？
Yeah, you can.
嗯，你可以直接说。
I think it's not only someone that inspires, but also knows when to take action.
我认为好的领导者不仅能鼓舞人心，而且知道何时该采取行动。
Okay.
好的。
Alright, agreed. Somebody with initiative, right?
嗯，同意。是具有主动性的人，对吧？
Yes, absolutely.
是的，完全正确。
I think both of these leaders were leaders who inspired others and took a great initiative.
我认为这两位领导者都曾鼓舞他人，并展现出卓越的主动性。
I would agree.
我同意。
Both of them were involved with some great liberal reforms as well.
他们两人也都参与了一些伟大的自由主义改革。
Alright, so we have a list of things that can help us to improve our English in particular reading and writing and speaking too since we'll be having a conversation throughout the entire lesson.
好了，这里列出了一些可以帮助我们提高英语水平，特别是读写能力，当然还有口语能力的方法，因为我们整个课程都会进行对话。
These are our class objectives.
这些是我们的课程目标。
Can you read the class objectives starting with this one here?
你能从这里第一个开始，读一下课程目标吗？
Yes, identify and explain the historical context of O-Captain, My Captain.
是的。识别并解释《啊，船长！我的船长！》的历史背景。
Define key vocabulary.
定义关键词汇。
For example,
例如，
?legy,
呃...挽歌 (wǎngē)？
keel, rack,
龙骨 (lónggǔ)，严峻的考验 (yánjùn de kǎoyàn)，
or is it
或者它是
elegy.
是挽歌 (wǎngē)。
And identify and extend it metaphor within the poem.
以及识别并解释诗中的扩展隐喻 (kuòzhǎn yǐnyù)。
Analyze the extended metaphor, explaining what the captain, ship, fearful trip and prize represent.
分析扩展隐喻 (kuòzhǎn yǐnyù)，解释船长、船、可怕的航行和奖赏分别代表什么。
Discuss the tone of the poem as it relates to grief and admiration.
讨论诗歌的基调，及其与悲伤和钦佩的关系。
And express understanding of the poem through discussion and written responses.
并通过讨论和书面回答来表达对诗歌的理解。
Okay.
好的。
Oh, and connect the poem's themes of loss, leadership, and national strategy to broader concepts of freedom.
哦，还有将诗歌中关于失落、领导力以及国家悲剧 (guójiā bēijù) 的主题与更广泛的自由概念联系起来。
Is it a freedom?
是自由 (zìyóu) 吗？
Like freedom.
比如自由。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, like freedom.
哦，比如自由。
Alright, so we have a lot that we can do.
好了，我们有很多事情可以做。
We might not have time to do all of this, but certainly there is a lot to digest about this poem.
我们可能没有时间做完所有这些，但关于这首诗，肯定有很多值得我们深入探讨 (shēnrù tàntǎo) 的地方。
And well, well, Whitman and historical context here.
还有，嗯，沃尔特·惠特曼以及这里的历史背景。
The vocabulary can be a little bit antiquated because it's, it was written in 1865 right after the assassination of Abraham Lincoln.
词汇可能有点过时，因为这首诗写于1865年，就在亚伯拉罕·林肯遇刺之后。
So I just want you to keep that in mind as we read this.
所以我希望你们在读这首诗的时候记住这一点。
There's a context to this poem.
这首诗是有背景的。
And maybe it's talking about something a little deeper.
而且它可能在谈论一些更深层次的东西。
So when we say extended metaphor, you know, a metaphor is when A is B.
所以当我们说扩展隐喻 (kuòzhǎn yǐnyù) 时，你知道，隐喻是A指代B。
But an extended metaphor is when maybe a whole paragraph or text is standing for something.
但是扩展隐喻可能是指整个段落或文本都在象征着某种东西。
Okay.
好的。
So some historical context here.
这里有一些历史背景。
But first here, what do you know about the American Civil War or Abraham Lincoln?
但首先，关于美国内战 (Měiguó Nèizhàn) 或亚伯拉罕·林肯，你知道些什么？
Oh, I know, I know the nickname honest Abe.
哦，我知道“诚实的艾布”这个绰号。
(The) American Civil War was specifically regarding slavery.
美国内战主要是关于奴隶制 (núlìzhì) 的，
If I'm not mistaken, correct?
如果我没记错的话，对吗？
Yes.
是的。
North and the South.
北方和南方之间的战争。
And then Abraham Lincoln.
然后是亚伯拉罕·林肯……
Well, you said the 16th president, but I think there's something.
嗯，您说了他是第16任总统，但我想还有些什么……
I think there was a very important decision he took and I can't quite remember it.
我想他做了一个非常重要的决定，但我记不太清了。
Something that he's really known about.
他因此而真正闻名的事情。
The emancipation proclamation.
《解放黑人奴隶宣言》(Jiěfàng Hēirén Núlì Xuānyán)。
Yeah.
是的。
All right.
没错。
Excellent.
非常好。
So you know some about the American Civil War in the context of this poem.
所以你对美国内战和这首诗的背景有所了解。
How important this was the Civil War in the United States.
内战在美国是何等重要。
Didn't just affect the United States had a cascade effect to other countries.
它不仅影响了美国，还对其他国家产生了连锁效应 (liánsuǒ xiàoyìng)。
And really changed a lot of attitudes.
并且确实改变了很多人的态度。
And it wasn't over at the end of the Civil War.
而且内战结束时，一切并没有结束。
And it's still not over.
至今仍未结束。
Really, we still fight with inequality.
说真的，我们仍在与不平等作斗争。
We still fight with issues related to slavery around the world.
我们仍在与世界各地与奴隶制相关的问题作斗争。
And this question about what it really means to be free.
以及这个关于真正自由意味着什么的问题。
And it's still an uphill battle.
这仍然任重道远 (rènzhòngdàoyuǎn)。
So we what Whitman wrote, oh, captain, my captain in 1865 shortly after two major events here.
所以沃尔特·惠特曼在1865年写下了《啊，船长！我的船长！》，这正是在两件大事发生后不久。
Can you read this part for us?
你能为我们读一下这部分吗？
Of course, the end of the Civil War, which lasted from 1861 to 1865.
当然。内战的结束，这场战争从1861年持续到1865年。
A rural conflict that divided the nation.
一场分裂了国家的残酷冲突 (cánkù chōngtū)。
And the assassination of President Abraham Abraham Lincoln in April 1865 just days after the Confederates surrender.
以及1865年4月亚伯拉罕·林肯总统遇刺，就在南方邦联投降几天之后。
Lincoln was seen by many as the captain who had steered the nation.
许多人将林肯视为引领国家这艘船的船长。
the ship... through the fearful trip of the war.
这艘船…驶过了战争这段可怕的航程。
So we see an example of a metaphor already the nation as the ship he steered it he was the captain.
所以我们已经看到了一个隐喻的例子：国家如船，他驾驶着它，他是船长。
in this poem that we're going to read.
在我们即将读到的这首诗中。
So that we have another colored picture of Abraham Lincoln.
这里有另一张亚伯拉罕·林肯的彩色照片。
I just think it's cool that they can put color to old pictures now.
我觉得现在能给老照片上色真是太酷了。
And it makes it look real.
让它看起来很真实。
And a scene from something that you would have seen in the newspaper.
还有一个场景，像是你会在报纸上看到的那样。
So Abraham Lincoln was in a theater when he was shot and assassinated.
亚伯拉罕·林肯是在一家剧院被枪击并遇刺的。
All right.
好的。
So here we have some terms that we need to know.
这里有一些我们需要了解的术语。
And you might hesitate with some of these vocabulary words.
对于这些词汇中的一些，你可能会有些犹豫。
They're a little difficult.
它们有点难。
So we have lyric, elegy, metaphor and extended metaphor.
我们有抒情诗 (shūqíngshī)，挽歌 (wǎngē)，隐喻 (yǐnyù) 和扩展隐喻 (kuòzhǎn yǐnyù)。
Lyric poetry is poetry that expresses personal emotions or feelings.
抒情诗是表达个人情感或感受的诗歌。
It's typically spoken in the first person.
通常以第一人称叙述。
So the poem that we're about to read is lyric poetry.
所以我们即将读到的这首诗是抒情诗。
And this one, remember the pronunciation, elegy, could you read this for us?
还有这个，记住发音，挽歌 (wǎngē)。你能为我们读一下这个吗？
Yes.
是的。
A poem of serious reflection, typically a lament for the dead.
一首严肃反思的诗，通常是为逝者写的哀歌。
Oh, captain, my captain is an elegy for Abraham Lincoln.
《啊，船长！我的船长！》是为亚伯拉罕·林肯写的挽歌。
All right.
没错。
So we're talking about someone a captain who was killed.
所以我们谈论的是一位被杀害的船长。
And so the poem is really deep.
因此这首诗意境深远。
And it's a little dark in that sense.
从某种意义上说，它有点黑暗。
You have to imagine the feeling at the end of a war.
你必须想象战争结束时的那种感觉。
The feeling at the end of the war is one of relief.
战争结束时的感觉可能是一种解脱。
you could imagine, but also great sadness.
你可以想象，但同时也有巨大的悲伤。
You can't bring back the lives that were lost.
你无法挽回逝去的生命。
You can't undo what was done.
你无法撤销已经发生的事情。
What was done was done.
木已成舟 (mù yǐ chéng zhōu)。
We have a metaphor, a figure of speech in which a word or phrase is applied.
我们有隐喻，这是一种修辞手法，将一个词或短语应用于……
So when one thing is another, and then this extension of that, the extended metaphor.
所以当一事物是另一事物时，然后是它的延伸，即扩展隐喻。
Could you read this one for us?
你能为我们读一下这个吗？
Yes.
是的。
A metaphor that is developed over several lines of writing or even throughout an entire work.
一种在几行文字甚至整个作品中展开的隐喻。
Great.
很好。
So here's the first reading.
这是第一次朗读。
I'll read this first one for you.
这第一部分我来读。
I want you to listen to the way that this sounds.
我希望你仔细听听这听起来是怎样的。
While follow eyes and steady keel.
众目睽睽紧随平稳的龙骨，
The vessel grim and daring.
船只阴沉而无畏。
But oh, heart, heart, heart.
但是，哦，心啊，心啊，心啊！
Oh, the bleeding drops of red.
哦，那鲜红的血滴，
Where on the deck, my captain lies, fallen cold and dead.
在甲板上，我的船长躺在那里，冰冷地逝去。
So we have this image of a ship with a keel.
所以我们看到了这艘带有龙骨 (lónggǔ) 的船的形象。
So certain part of the ship, right?
船的某个特定部分，对吧？
The vessel grim and daring.
阴沉而无畏的船只。
You see this dark ship entering.
你看到这艘阴暗的船驶入。